ATHM Textile Industry Cloth Labels 6524/003 MB
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series I: Arranged Alphabetically
  - K, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Item 6: King Phillip Mills Fine Cambric Muslin, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 7)
      Fall River, Mass.: King Philip Mills, ca. 1890s. Image of woman wearing (muslin?) petticoat under robe with maid putting on her shoes; open fan in background. 25.5 x 20 cm.
  - L, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Extra Soft Finish. L. & B., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Salisbury & Co. Lith. 159 Duane St. N.Y. N.p., n.d. Crest of anchors within orange frame against cream background. 13.5 x 15.5 cm.
    - Item 2: No. 13 36 Yds, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      No. 13 36 Yds. N.p., n.d. Black lettering and decorations against cream background. 9.5 x 16 cm.
    - Item 3: Laconia Mills, Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Boston. Biddeford, Me.: Laconia Co., ca. 1845-1899. Image of peacock in center in gold with lettering surrounded by a wreath of flowers below against white background. 13.5 x 17.5 cm. Identical to Items 4 and 5, in this folder, except for colors.
    - Item 4: Laconia Mills, Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Boston. Biddeford, Me.: Laconia Co., ca. 1845-1899. Image of peacock in center in gold with lettering surrounded by a wreath of flowers below against yellow background. 13.5 x 17.5 cm. Identical to Items 3 and 5, in this folder, except for colors.
    - Item 5: Laconia Mills, Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Boston. Biddeford, Me.: Laconia Co., ca. 1845-1899. Image of peacock in center in gold with lettering surrounded by a wreath of flowers below against green background. 13.5 x 17.5 cm. Identical to Items 3 and 4, in this folder, except for colors.
    - Item 6: Warranted Perfect Full Madder Colors Best A Cloth, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      By the Laconia Print Works. John Coffey, Agent. Laconia, N.H.? ca. 1800s. Gray background with black and white letters and gold bordering. 6.5 x 8 cm.
    - Item 7: Ladies' Collars and Cuffs, One Set, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      No. _____ Size ____. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against cream background. 7.75 x 2.5 cm.
    - Item 8: Ladies' Choice Warranted 64 x 64 Cambrics, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      ____Yds. W.H. Forbes & Co. [Lithographer]. N.p., ca. 1868-1875. Black lettering against red background within gold border. 11 x 15 cm.
    - Item 9: Lakeview Fine Silesias, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Middlesex Bleachy. And Dye Works. W.H. Forbes Lith. Boston. N.p.,ca. 1860s. Black and gray lettering against light tan background within dark gold border. 8 x 12 cm.
    - Item 10: Lakewood, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering against white banner; red, black and gold background. 23 x 18.5 cm.
    - Item 11: Lakewood Woolen Mills, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Case _____ Style _____ No. _____ Yds. _____. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against white background. 7 x 8.75 cm.
    - Item 12: Lancashire Warranted Fast Colors, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      ____ Yds. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering within white oval surrounded by gold and black frame. 14.5 x 11.5 cm.
    - Item 13: Lancaster Blue Drills Warranted Indigo, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Yards. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against orange background. 25.5 x 20.5 cm.
    - Item 14: Lancaster cambric, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      ____Yds. Clinton, Mass.: Lancaster Mills, ca. 1800s. Image of young woman from waist up in center, surrounded by gold and red frame. 10.5 x 14.5 cm.
    - Item 15: Lancaster Extra Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      _____Yds. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against cream background. 18.5 x 23 cm.
    - Item 16: Lancaster Extra Heavy Wigans, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Clinton, Mass.: Lancaster Mills, ca. 1800s. Gold lettering against deep purple background. 11 x 14.5 cm.
    - Item 17: Lancaster Superfine Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Clinton, Mass.: Lancaster Mills, ca. 1800s. Black lettering against cream/white background within red border. 18 x 13.75 cm.
    - Item 18: Lancaster Mills dress styles, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Upham Tucker & Co. Agents. Boston & New York. Case _____ Style ________. Forbes Co. Boston & N.Y. [Clinton, Mass.: Lancaster Mills, ca. 1860s. Label pasted onto paper. 11 x 13.5 cm. (dimensions are of label, not paper)
    - Item 19: Lancaster Mills Gingham, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Power Loom. Fast Colors. No. ______ ____ Yds. Caleb Defley, Printer. Clinton, Mass.: Lancaster Mills, ca. 1800s. Gold lettering against a gray background, within a green and gold border. 8.25 x 12.25 cm.
    - Item 20: Lancaster Mills Ginghams, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Style ___________ ________ Yds. [Clinton, Mass.]: Lancaster Mills, ca. 1800s. Engraving (?) of mill complex in center. 15.5 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 21: Lancaster Percale Robes: Latest Paris Styles, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Waist & upper skirt 8 yds - lower skirt 4 yrds. N.E. Lith.Steam Prtg. Co. 34 Chauncy St. Boston. [Clinton, Mass.: Lancaster Mills, ca. 1860s. Image of young woman from side view, wearing green-striped dress over green striped petticoat, holding fan. 9.
    - Item 22: Lancaster prints Yds., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Yds. Clinton, Mass.: Lancaster Mills, ca. 1800s. Image of female warrior with shield and spear, set in niche. 11 x 17 cm.
    - Item 23: Landseer's Best Fine Cottons, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      N.p., n.d. Image of two dogs in center doorway; black lettering against gold and tan background. 19.75 x 25 cm.
    - Item 24: Langdon Manf'g. Co. GB J.L. Bremer, Brother & Co., 1876; Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Boston, New York & Phila. Engraved and printed by the National Bank-Note Co., New York. Manchester, N.H.: Langdon Manufacturing Company. Gray, white and black. 24.5 x 19.5 cm.
    - Item 25: Langdon Manf'g. Co. '76 J.L. Bremer, Brother & Co., 1876; Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Item 26: Langdon Manufacturing Co. Manchester, N.H., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      F.F. Oakley's Lith 204 Washn. St. Boston [Lithographer]. ca. 1860s. Red and gold lettering against white background. 20 x 16 cm.
    - Item 27: "Seventy six", 1876; Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Manchester, N.H. Manchester, N.H.: Langdon Manufacturing Company. Image of woman carrying flag and sword leading Revolutionary-era soldiers. 18.5 x 24 cm.
    - Item 28: Langdon vest paddings., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Manchester, N.H.: Langdon Manufacturing Company, ca. 1860s. Gold lettering against white background. 11.25 x 15 cm.
    - Item 29: Gardner Brewer & Co., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Boston New York & Phila. Langdon Manuf'g. Co. Manchester, N.H. Gardner Brewer were agents for Langdon. Manchester, N.H.: Langdon Manuf'g Co., ca. 1860s. Gold lettering against cream background with gold border. Label has been measured horizontally, a
    - Item 30: Lastings, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed; blue lettering on white background, enclosed by gold and green border. 15 x 8.5 cm.
    - Item 31: Lastings, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering against white background, within gold and black border. 25 x 9 cm.
    - Item 32: Lastings, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      N.p., n.d. Blue lettering against a white background, set within an elaborate embossed frame of lavender and gold. 17.25 x 8.5 cm.
    - Item 33: Latest Styles, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      No. Yds. N.p., n.d. black lettering within elabor border of flowers and leaves against white background. 11 x 14.5 cm.
    - Item 34: Lawns. Warranted Perfect and Fast Colors, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      No. __ Yds. __. N.p., n.d. Black lettering with gold image in center of wolfhound's (?) head over crown. 7 x 10 cm. (folded)
    - Item 35: B Lawns Warranted Perfect and Fast Colors, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      ___ Yds. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering with gold image in center of wolfhound's (?) head over crown. 7 x 10.5 cm. (folded)
    - Item 36: Lawrence Bleachery and Dyeworks, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Lawrence, Mass.?: Lawarence Bleachery and Dyeworks, n.d. Gold lettering against a purple background; label is in the form of a diamond. 10 x 10 cm.
    - Item 37: Lawrence Mills color permanent., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Lawrence, Mass.: Lawrence Mills, before 1892. Black lettering against red bands; orange, red and gold border. 26.5 x 21.5 cm.
    - Item 38: Lawrence XXX Sleeve Linings, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering against blue background. 12 x 10 cm.
    - Item 39: Leavensworth Superfine Jeans, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Yds. Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works, Somerville, Mass. N.p., n.d. Green lettering against cream background. 14 x 17 cm.
    - Item 40: Lewiston bleachery finish., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Lewiston, Me.: Lewiston Bleachery and Dye Works, n.d. Shield with Lewiston on banner across shield, against background of American flags. 9.5 x 9.5 cm. (on diagonal)
    - Item 41: Lewiston Bleachery Finish, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Lewiston, Me.: Lewiston Bleachery and Dye Works, n.d. Shield with Lewiston on banner across shield, against background of American flags. 9.5 x 9.5 cm. (on diagonal) Copy 2.
    - Item 42: Lewiston Mills Finish, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Lewiston, Me.? Lewiston Bleachery and Dye Works? ca. 1800s. Embossed; gold lettering and animal's head (mountain lion?) in center; red border. 9 x 9 cm. (on diagonal)
    - Item 43: Lewiston Mills, Lewison, Maine., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      ca. 1861-1886. Green lettering against white background, surrounded by ivy design. 15.5 x 10.5 cm.
    - Item 44: Leominister Suiting, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Warranted free from cotton or shoddy. Edwd. M. Rockwell, Leominster, Mass. Style ___ Case ___ No. ___ Yds. ___. Leominster, Mass.: Edwd. M. Rockwell, ca. 1900. White lettering on black banners and black lettering against white background. 6.5 x 9.5 c
    - Item 45: Lewiston Toilet Quilt, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering with cow's head in center against green background in black and gold border. 9.75 x 13.5 cm. Toilet quilt is another term for toilet cloth.
    - Item 46: Liberty Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Yds. N.p., n.d. Image in center of Revolutionary War-era figures, one with flag, with Constitution & Laws behind them; banner at top of image reads E Pluribus Unum. Dark gold background. 16.5 x 20.5 cm.
    - Item 47: Liberty Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Yds. N.p., n.d. Image in center of Revolutionary War-era figures, one with flag, with Constitution & Laws behind them; banner at top of image reads E Pluribus Unum. Black and white photocopy. 16.5 x 20.5 cm.
    - Item 48: Lily of the Valley Heavy Family Cottons, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Trade-Mark. N.p., n.d. Image of lilies of the valley in center niche against black background; gold lettering against tan background. 20 x 24.75 cm.
    - Item 49: Golden fleece, Lincoln Mill, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      No. 170 wool-mixed 66 x 80. [Lewiston, Me.]: Lincoln Mill, ca. 1900s. Image of ancient warriors (Roman? Greek?) on boat in center. 15.75 x 13 cm.
    - Item 50: Superior Quality Linen Cambric Handkerchiefs, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed; two female faces in gold niches flank bird in center set in gold niche, with gold design around edges. 11 x 4.5 cm.
    - Item 51: Superior Quality Linen Cambric Handkerchiefs, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Registered Trademark Industria Permanente. Prize medal 1876 Philadelphia. Gold medal 1878 Paris. No. 187. N.p., ca. 1878. Embossed; gold and silver background. 4.5 x 6 cm.
    - Item 52: Warranted All Pure Linen Best Quality, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed; gold lettering within gold frame. 6 x 8.5 cm.
    - Item 53: Fancy Linseys, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Manufactured by R. & A. Kennedy. Plainfield Conn., No. _______ _____ Yards. Plainfield, Conn.: R. & A. Kennedy, ca. 1800s. Black lettering against white background. 12.5 x 9 cm.
    - Item 54: Linweave Lawn, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Dept. 22, trade mark. Qual._____ No._____ Yds._____
    - Item 55: Listado Mijo, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Striped Millet?. N.p., ca. 1900s. Spanish. Image of crocodile or alligator on shore next to palm trees. 16.5 x 21.5 cm.
    - Item 56: Llama Cloth 25 Inches Wide, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Llama Cloth 25 Inches Wide. No. ___ ___ Metr. At top of label: Royal Gold Medal. N.p., n.d. Shield in center with allegorical figures above. 9.25 x 14 cm.
    - Item 57: New Llama Persian For This Season, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      No. 41 Yds. N.p., n.d. Lavender, gold, and green lettering set against a white background, framed with gold and white flowers and green ferns, set against a lavender background. 8.75 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 58: Lola Sleeve Lining, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      N.p., n.d. Red lettering within an oval frame, against a cream background. 10.5 x 14 cm.
    - Item 59: London W Cambrics, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      No____________Yds. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering and design against white background. 9.5 x 13.5 cm.
    - Item 60: London Crinkled Seersucker, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Style ____ Yds. _____ Case ____. From Farr Alpaca Company. N.p., n.d. White lettering against gold background. 7.5 x 10.5 cm.
    - Item 61: Lonsdale, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Item 62: Lonsdale Co. Super Fine Cambric Muslin, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Item 63: Lot "77", Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      ____Yards. N.p., n.d. Gold lettering against white background, surrounded by gold and gray border. 7.5 x 10.5 cm.
    - Item 64: 1 lb. thread manufactured and warranted by James Lothrop, Easton Mass., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      ca. 1800s. Black lettering against cream background. 11 x 15.5 cm.
    - Item 65: Lowell, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Lowell, Mass.: Unknown mill, n.d. Dark gold lettering against light gold background. 7.5 x 7.5 cm. (on diagonal)
    - Item 66: Lowell Bleachery and Dye Works, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Lowell, Mass.: Lowell Bleachery & Dye Works, ca. 1800s. Black lettering on urn, surrounded by black frame. 10 x 12 cm. Label has been slightly clipped in upper left corner.
    - Item 67: Lowell Cambric A, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      ____Yds. Forbes & Co. Lith. Lowell, Mass.: Unknown mill, ca. 1868-1875. Gold and black shield within circle. 11 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 68: Lowell Bleachry & Dye Works No....Yds., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      No. ________ Yds. Lowell, Mass.: Lowell Bleachery & Dye Works, ca. 1800s. Image of Crusader knight on horse in center carrying flag with company name on it. 10 x 13.5 cm.
    - Item 69: Lowell Cambric Glove Finish, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      ____Yds. Lowell, Mass.: Unknown mill, n.d. Heraldic shield in center circle. White background with gold circle and border. 11 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 70: Lowell Fancies, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      T.R. Marvin & Son, Prs. Lowell, Mass.: Unknown mill, ca. 1860-1900. Red lettering against white background with blue and gold frame. 18 x 14 cm.
    - Item 71: Lowell Mills Cassimeres Extra Heavy For Men's Wear, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      T.R. Marvin & Son, Prs. Lowell, Mass.: Unknown mill, ca. 1860-1900. Red oval surrounded by black and gold frame, within blue and gold border. 19 x 15 cm.
    - Item 72: The attention of the trade is called to the fact that by the introduction of entirely new machinery, 1870; Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      The attention of the trade is called to the fact that by the introduction of entirely new machinery, we are enabled to maufacture this popular brand of bleached muslin with a degree of uniformity in weight and count not before attained by us. Lowell, Jul
    - Item 73: Superfine Lucca Oil, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Imported by W.K. Lewis & Bros. 93 Broad St., Boston. Boston: W.K. Lewis & Bros., ca. 1880s. Gold lettering and design on white background. Lucca oil is olive oil from a particular area of Tuscany; W.K. Lewis & Bros. were possibly foodstuff importers.
    - Item 74: Lyman Mills Cambric, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Holyoke, Mass.: Lyman Mills, n.d. Gold lettering against white background. 18.25 x 11.25 cm.
    - Item 75: Lyman Mills extra quality., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Holyoke, Mass.: Lyman Mills, n.d. Embossed; gold lettering against red background. 5.5 x 5.5 cm.
    - Item 76: Lyman Mills H Blue drills, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Warranted Indigo Blue. Middlesex Bleachery and Dye Works, Somerville, Mass. Holyoke, Mass.: Lyman Mills, n.d. Black lettering against orange background. 24 x 19.5 cm.
    - Item 77: Lyman Mills silk finish., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 8)
      Holyoke, Mass.: Lyman Mills, n.d. Embossed; gold lettering and design against red background. 26 x 8 cm.
  - M, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: M 8 Oz., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering against blue background; red, gold and brown border. 16.5 x 20.5 cm.
    - Item 2: M 40, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering on extremely thin paper. 16.5 x 5 cm.
    - Item 3: M. C., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      N.p., n.d. Embossed; gold letters and design on deep purple background. 6.25 x 8 cm.
    - Item 4: Made From the Purest Flax M.L.H. & Co. Philadelphia, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Grass Bleached. Philadelphia, Pa.: M.L.H. & Co., n.d. Embossed; gold lettering and bundle of flax. 5.5 x 8 cm.
    - Item 5: M R All Silk 7 Belts, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      N.p., n.d. Design repeated on label. Gold lettering against white/cream background. 14.5 x 7.25 cm.
    - Item 6: M R Warranted 7 Belts, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      N.p., n.d. Gold and black lettering on white/cream background. 6.5 x 6.5 cm.
    - Item 7: Madras Bunting, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      N.p., n.d. Image of camel's head in lower left-hand corner. Black lettering and border. 14.5 x 8.5 cm.
    - Item 8: Magnolis Superfine Corset Jeans, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      N.p., n.d. Gold lettering set within elaborate frame. 12 x 17.5 cm.
    - Item 9: Majestic, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      N.p., n.d. Image of deer (buck) in center medallion, surrounded by gold and red frame. 23.5 x 18.75 cm.
    - Item 10: Malcolm Ross & Sons, Manchester, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Trade mark. Vincit Veritas. Manchester, [Eng.], n.d. Gold lettering, crest and border on dark pink background. Company manufactured and exported cotton yarn. 7.5 x 10.5 cm.
    - Item 11: Malcolm Ross & Sons, Manchester, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Trade mark. Vincit Veritas. Manchester, [Eng.], n.d. Gold lettering, crest and border on dark pink background. Company manufactured and exported cotton yarn. 7.5 x 10.5 cm. Copy 2.
    - Item 12: Malcolm Ross & Sons, Manchester, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Trade mark. Vincit Veritas. Manchester, [Eng.], n.d. Gold lettering, crest and border on dark pink background. Company manufactured and exported cotton yarn. 7.5 x 10.5 cm. Copy 3.
    - Item 13: Manchester, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      N.p., n.d. Lithograph; yellow/gold/blue/green/purple; crest with Latin motto "Nemo Me Impune Lacesset" (No one provokes me with impunity) on left, thistle on right. 22.5 x 17 cm.
    - Item 14: Manchester, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      No. ___ ___ Yds. N.p., ca. 1870. Image of woman in dress with mantle over it, wearing hat and carrying open parasol. 10 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 15: Manchester fine corset jeans, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Middlesex Bleachery [&] Dye Works. T.R. Marvin & Son, Prs., Somerville, Mass.: Middlesex Bleachery & Dye Works, n.d. Lavender and green lettering against gold background, within lavender and green frame. 12.75 x 17 cm.
    - Item 16: Manchester Counterpanes, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      11/4. N.p., n.d. Red lettering against cream background, surrounded by red border. 14.5 x 10.25 cm.
    - Item 17: Manchester De Laines, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      N.p., n.d. Image is the coat of arms of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts: shield, with Native American in center of shield and banner below that reads "Ense Petit Placidam Sub Libertate Quietem" (By the sword we seek peace, but peace only under liberty)
    - Item 18: Real Manchester Ginghams Warranted Fast Colors, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      James, Kent, Santee & Co., Philadelphia. Philadelphia, Pa.? ca. 1800s. Embossed; gold lettering and design against a blue background. 11 x 7.5 cm.
    - Item 19: Manchester Print Works, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Manchester, N.H.: Manchester Mills, ca. 1800s. Engraved; black and white. Two children on horse in center, with large dog at feet of horse with another child. 11.5 x 16 cm.
    - Item 21: The Manchester Print Works., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Manchester N.H., ca. 1800s. Engraved; mill complex in center with river on left and railroad train on right. Removed from frame; framed with Box 3, Folder 6, Item 46. Copy 2. 16 x 12 cm.
    - Item 22: Manchester Print Works Warranted Pure Madder Colors, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      "Manchester Print Works Warranted Pure Madder Colors" motto over an oval depicting an image of a waterfall with trees on the left and buildings in the distant background. Oval is mounted on a block with the number "371" written on it in ink. Floral bord
    - Item 23: Manchester Print Works Full madder colors., Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Manchester, N.H.: Manchester Mills, ca. 1800s. Engraved/black & white. Two classical figures, boy and girl. 14 x 19.5 cm.
    - Item 24: Manchester Print works, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Incorporated 1839. Manchester N.H.: Manchester Mills, ca. 1800s. Engraved; shows mill complex with river on left and railroad in foreground. 17.5 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 25: The Manchester Print Works, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Manchester N.H.: Manchester Mills, ca. 1800s. Engraved; mill complex in center with river on left and railroad train on right. 16.5 x 12.5 cm.
    - Item 26: Manchester Print Works, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Manchester, N.H.: Manchester Mills, ca. 1800s. Engraved; Mill complex in center, with group of people in foreground and large hay wagon at left. 12 x 16.5 cm.
    - Item 27: Manchester Print Works, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Incorporated 1839. Manchester, N.H.: Manchester Mills, ca. 1800s. Engraved; image of mill complex. 12 x 15.5 cm.
    - Item 28: Manchester Steam Mills, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      B.F. Allen [printer?]. Manchester, N.H.?, n.d. Gold and red lettering within elaborate gold and red frame. 20.5 x 16 cm.
    - Item 29: Manchester Steam Mills, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Manchester, N.H.?, n.d. Gold lettering against white background. 16.5 x 14.5 cm.
    - Item 30: Manhattan Beach Lawns, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Style No. _____ _____Yds. N.p., n.d. Red lettering within a gold border against a white background. 6.75 x 9.5 cm.
    - Item 31: Manhattan Blue Drills Warranted Indigo Blue, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Yds. N.p., n.d. Black lettering against orange background. 25.25 x 20.5 cm.
    - Item 32: Manhattan Sleeve Linings, Cloth label (Box 2, Folder 9)
      Extra Quality. N.p., n.d. Embossed; red lettering within gold border. 8.5 x 13 cm.